4 Years Ago
Year 1, Class 1
Komichi Aya
I-I'm Komichi Aya.
I'll be in your class from now on.
Komichi Aya
All right, Komichi-san. Take the open seat right there.
O-Okay.
She's so cute!
I wonder if we can be friends!
Komichi Aya
Hello there!
H-Hello.
Good morning.
O-Oomiya-san!
G-Good morning.
Good morning, Aya-chan.
You can call me Shino.
O-Okay then...
Sh-Shino...
She knows my love by the color of my face.
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
Hyakunin Isshu?
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
She knows my love
by the color
of my face
Shino and I have been friends since middle school.
But...
I want to see you
aitai na
I want to see you too
aitai ne
I'm sure our wish
kitto negaigoto
will come true
kanau kara
kin-iroâœ¦mosaic
-
Let's head out
issho ni ikou
All together wherever we go
donna basho mo minna de
Let's shine with smiles brighter than the blinding sun
niconico de mabushii taiyou yori mo kagayakou
I found a five-leaf clover yesterday
kinou mitsuketa itsutsu no ha no kuroobaa
Strange, isn't it? I feel like a miracle's going to happen
fushigi da ne kiseki ga okiru yokan shiterunda
With all of us together, we're at full strength
minna wa minna de omoikiri jan
Will we get there? Can you see it? It's the future
nee todoku ka na? mieru ka na? mirai ga
Cha
Chance!
Full power
seiippai
Say hello!
say hello
A wonderful fate
saikou na unmei
and sparkling dreams
kirari kirari kanaetai yume
lie in store for us
madamada aru kara
Always smiling
zettai sumairu
never worrying
mondai nai
That's how we've lived
sou yatte kitanda yo
When the flowers of the world bloom
sekaijuu de hana hiraku toki
Let's be smiling
egao de iyou ne
Moegi High School
When I shout "I'm home!"
ookiku "tadaima" shite
We'll answer back "Welcome home!"
"okaeri" tte iitai na
Like a close-knit family
nandemo wakaru kazoku mitai
Always and forever
itsumo itsuma demo
Aya-chan?
Seriously?
I'm begging you...
Please show up on time...
A-Are you okay?
Aya?
Ayaya needs to get in better shape.
Sorry, I've been a little sluggish in the mornings lately.
Not enough sleep?
Even this morning...
One moment, I had just gotten out of bed...
Shino, wake up already!
The next, I was all ready to head out the door!
Alice did everything for you!
Shino, are you tired?
Does it look that way?
Shino's spending a lot of time at home
preparing for the festival.
Class A's doing a play, right?
And Shino's writing the script?
Yes!
I'm putting the finishing touches on it right now,
but it's like I've been using
a part of my brain I usually don't...
Maybe that's why I'm so sleepy.
Why don't you use that part of your brain more often?
Shino...
Geez, you have enough on your plate with the script,
yet you still volunteered to make the costumes?
But thanks to Shino, this is gonna be a fun play!
I can't wait to see the script!
Please wait just a little longer.
I know you're really excited about this,
but you still need to make sure to be on time.
Oh, I know! Should I give you a wake-up call in the morning?
Wow, a morning call!
No way! I'd feel bad about that.
Then how about I come pick you up, like in the old days?
Youko did that?
When we were in elementary school, Youko-chan came to pick me up before school.
But Youko overslept today too.
Guess so!
Sorry, scrap that plan then.
Don't worry! I'll make sure you get here on time!
Alice!
You're going to wake me up no matter how sleepy I am?
Since elementary school...
I'd do anything for you, Shino!
Ayaya, please come pick me up every morning!
You're fine on your own.
The school festival will be this month.
While I'm sure you'll all be busy working on it,
please be mindful not to neglect your studies.
I'm really looking forward to the school festival!
Me too!
Shino's doing the screenplay and costumes,
so are you acting again, Karen?
Yes!
And in a lead role this year!
You can pin your hopes on me.
I feel like you said that last year too.
What about you, Aya?
I'll be working backstage, of course.
Aw!
But I wanted to see you shine!
You're too close!
Why?
Well, I'm not surprised Shino's this excited.
Really?
She's enjoyed this kind of stuff since elementary school.
I see!
And she used to be even spacier,
but whenever she gets into something,
she turns into a different person!
So she's always been like this?
And you haven't changed a bit since elementary school, Youko-chan.
Hey, don't make it sound like I haven't grown up at all!
I'm off to pick the stuff up!
Let's go with this color.
Yeah, that works great!
Shinobu-chan, I'll leave the extras over here, okay?
Thank you very much.
Impressive.
Youko-chan! Alice!
Medieval European clothes must be hard to make.
I'll leave this to you.
Sure.
Shino, don't overwork yourself.
We'll help if you want!
Even if we're in a different class.
Thank you very much!
But I'm fine.
It's very fulfilling work, not to mention fun!
Come, Karen.
Here's your third for the day.
Power Max
Gold
Here, here!
What happened to my ideal Japanese woman?!
Oh yeah, Shino went all-out for our elementary school plays too.
Yes, I've always liked them.
She went all "I'm a princess!" when she put on this super flowery dress!
Wow!
I've been thinking about some things these days.
Youko-chan, that was so long ago!
And then!
Shino and I have been friends since middle school.
But...
That outfit would have been lovely with your golden blonde hair.
We don't go back as far as she and Youko-chan do.
Really?
And I don't have blonde hair like Alice and Karen.
Then what about me?
You would look good too, Karen.
It's possible that Shino doesn't consider me...
...as close a friend as I consider her.
No, there's no way.
There's no way, right?
You and I are best friends!
She's getting anxious about something again.
Ayaya! Where are you going?
I think she's taking those costume samples to Kuzehashi-sensei.
It looks like we'll be busy through the weekend.
If you're bringing this home, I'll help out!
I'll come along!
Honoka, you too.
Sorry, I need to practice my performance
with the tennis club over the weekend.
What are you performing?
Ball balancing and juggling!
What?! Are you doing a circus?
But...
We're coming in!
Be our guests, you two.
Come on in!
Isn't that our middle school uniform?
And Isa-nee's high school uniform?
Exactly!
They're a bit big, but they look great!
Isn't it just lovely?
We can have sailor uniforms
and blonde hair together!
Enjoying yourself as always, Shino.
You girls look like you're having fun.
'Sup, Isa-nee!
H-Hello.
Hi! Welcome, Youko-chan, Aya-chan.
Come on in. Sorry it's a mess.
Oh, so this is the princess costume.
Looks like it's almost done.
Oh, Karen!
You'll get in our way if you read manga there.
Everything going well?
Yes. I've finished who knows how many
costumes yesterday and today.
Good going.
The costumes Shino made are all wonderful!
The screenplay's a masterpiece too!
When you compare the capable Shino with the usual Shino, it's kinda befuddling.
True.
The princess costume is done!
Beautiful...
What's up, Aya?
Do you want to play the princess after all?
Th-That's not it!
You're amazing, Shino!
Put it on for us!
I want to see too!
I-If you insist, I suppose I cannot let you down.
Please don't react too strongly when you see me turn into a princess.
Ta-da!
How is it?
You're so cute you could start a big bang!
You dote on Shino too much.
I think she looks normal.
By the way, Shino, is the prince costume ready yet?
Oh yeah, is Class C's project going well?
I heard Alice was really excited about it.
Yeah, it's called "Heart of Japan, Heart of Wa".
You guys should come by.
Sure.
Well, it's really easy since there's Japanese stuff all over the place anyway.
We're going to offer rice, miso soup, grilled fish...
So just... Japanese food?
fidget
What's the matter? You're being fidgety.
I'm a little thirsty and all we have is green tea, so I'm going to the store.
That's fine. I'll make some green tea.
N-No!
I feel like black tea right now!
There's some other stuff I want to buy, so Onee-chan's going to come with me.
Then I'll go with you too.
It's okay, we'll be fine.
I-I see.
Just sit tight and wait for me!
And off!
Shino!
She left.
Very suspicious!
She's gotta be planning something.
Let's follow her!
Well, even if she's up to something,
I'm sure it's just a nice surprise.
Just play along and pretend you didn't see it coming.
Youko, you know her so well!
I've known her forever, after all.
That, and she's too easy to read!
Right, Aya?
Why are you making that face?
No reason.
I wonder what the surprise'll be!
Could it be a present for Alice and Karen?
You think so?
My imagination is overflowing!
Fidget fidget!
What's with that dance?
It's the fidget fidget dance!
Looking again, you two sure look great
in Shino and Isa-nee's old uniforms.
Your old middle school uniforms are so cute!
Isami's is also very cute!
Right?
Alice, let's proceed to part two
of the fidget fidget dance!
Okay!
Repeat after me!
All right!
Fidget fidget...
Aya?
Is something wrong?
N-No, of course not.
I just got a little sentimental reminiscing about our middle school days.
I see, sentimental!
That's English, you know!
Speaking of middle school,
there's something I've always wanted to know.
How did Shino get into high school?
She took the test!
And she passed just like everyone else!
B-But how did she do it without blonde hair power?!
Alice wasn't here for her, you know!
Well, I kinda get where you're coming from...
I want to know how Shino passed her entrance exams too.
All right, all right.
I'll tell you.
Really?
Yay!
Once upon a time, in a land far away...
Youko?
Um, is something wrong?
Huh?
Telling the story like an old lady?
Of course.
2 Years Ago, Summer
"Thanks" is
...a warm and
......wonderful word
"Thanks" is
...a warm and
......wonderful word
Only now I realize,
you've always been
by me, smiling
Year 3, Class 2
Explain yourself!
You're failing!
Year 3, Class 2
Name
Oomiya Shinobu
Factor the following polynomials.
Factor the following polynomials.
Year 3, Class 2
Name
Oomiya Shinobu
Factor the following polynomials.
F
e
m
t
Year 3, Class 2
Name
Oomiya Shinobu
e
m
s
t
Year 3, Class 2
Name
Oomiya Shinobu
Year 3, Class 2
Name
Oomiya Shinobu
Year 3, Class 2
Name
Oomiya Shinobu
F
e
m
t
Year 3, Class 2
Name
Year 3, Class 2
Name
Factor the following polynomials.
Year 3, Class 2
Name
Oomiya Shinobu
Factor the following polynomials.
Year 3, Class 2
Factor the following polynomials.
Year 3, Class 2
Factor the following polynomials.
Year 3, Class 2
Name
Oomiya Shinobu
Factor the following polynomials.
Year 3, Class 2
Year 3, Class 2
Name
Oomiya Shinobu
F
e
m
t
Year 3, Class 2
Now, now. She was one question away from passing.
Youko, worry about your own grades first.
Yes, ma'am.
We're going to take our high school entrance exams soon.
What are you going to do with these grades?
Well, I don't really care as long as I get in somewhere.
Do you not care about your studies at all?
That's not what I...
Shino, what kind of high school
do you want to go to?
Ideally, I'd like to study abroad in England—
We didn't ask about your dreams!
N-No, that's really what I...
How about Isa-nee's school?
If you're at the same school, she can
help you get ready in the morning!
Shino's sister's school?
Where's that?
Um, let's see...
You can forget about it. That's way out of your league.
What about you, Aya?
Know where you want to go?
Kind of, I guess...
Suiren Girls' Academy?!
It has such a beautiful ring!
I've never heard of it.
Wait, Shino—are you serious?
Even I've heard of them!
They're a famous rich-girl school!
The uniforms are so cute!
My parents and teachers all recommended it.
They said I'd have a good chance with my grades...
Seriously? That's great, Aya!
That place suits you perfectly!
But it's kind of far away, so I'd probably end up living in a dorm.
Then... I wouldn't be able to see you two—
Wow! I'm so jealous!
You'll be a boarding school girl!
I wonder how they greet each other!
I bet they say "good day"!
Does the cafeteria serve western food?
There might even be blonde transfer students!
Aya?
Is something wrong?
I...
Could it be...
...that some other schools have caught your eye?
Good going, Youko-chan! You always
know what Aya-chan's thinking.
Pop
Th-That's right.
Wow, it's closer than I thought.
That's the uniform.
I want a parfait...
I think I've seen it around.
Shino?
What's up?
That uniform's great, isn't it?
I want to wear a uniform like that too!
This way.
Moegi High School
Moegi High School.
I've heard of it.
It's one of the more popular public high schools in the area.
It's also close by, and I love the feel.
Being close by is a plus!
Especially for sleepyhead Shino.
Bye-bye, Sensei!
Okay, goodbye.
Let's go somewhere.
Yeah, sure!
They're cute.
Here for a visit maybe?
We can go inside, right?
N-No, we can't!
Hello there.
W-We're sorry!
We're not up to anything, I swear...
Middle schoolers? Here to look around?
Um, yes!
Excuse me...
Are you a teacher here?
I sure am.
I can give you a tour if you want.
Yes!
Please!
Career Notebook
A lot of students bring their lunches and eat them out here.
Oh? A sunshower?
We can't go home until it stops.
Um, Sensei?
Do you think I can become a student here?
Huh?
Shino?
Of course you can.
As long as you pass the test.
Really?
H-Hold on a minute.
You need to consider your grades.
They'll go up as long as you keep studying.
But we're already third-years.
It's just not realistic.
Not to worry!
It's not even summer vacation yet.
Lots of students here made last-minute surges to get in.
And that includes none other than yours truly!
I actually graduated from this school.
Wow, I see!
I really liked this school, so I decided
I wanted to be a teacher here.
And before I knew it, I was!
I understand. It's important to dream!
Precisely.
Sh-Shino, it's also important to look at reality.
All right, I'll cast a spell to help you get in.
Fight!
Totem pole!
The Totem Pole Song
Get-into-high-school ver.
Lyrics: Karasuma Sakura
Composition: Karasuma Sakura
The Totem Pole Song
Get-into-high-school ver.
Lyrics: Karasuma Sakura
Composition: Karasuma Sakura
Everyone pass!
Do your best, do your best!
Fight!
Totem pole!
Thank you very much!
Come again anytime.
Aya-chan, Youko-chan.
I've decided.
I'm going to go to this school.
Um, come on. Be realistic.
Remember your test scores!
I'll just work really hard and improve my grades!
Then I'll pass for sure!
Shino...
Okay, then I'm going to go here too!
I really took a liking to it today!
Though it'll be just as hard for me as it'll be for Shino.
Still, we can't do this all by ourselves.
Please, Aya-chan!
Help us study!
Me too! Anything would help a lot!
I won't be going easy on you.
Are you committed?
Yes!
I'll give it my all.
Let's do our best, Youko-chan!
Yeah.
We'll pass for sure!
Hey, look!
It's a rainbow!
It must be a blessing from heaven.
I feel like we really can do this!
Beneath this rainbow lie both those who will pass and those who will fail.
Just focus on the ones who pass for now!
Do your best!
Target: Moegi High School!!
High School Entrance Exam Summer Vacation Study Schedule
Goal:
Study a little every day!!
Focus on your weaknesses and turn them into strengths!!
Math 40 points | Japanese 50 points | Science 40 points
Social Studies 50 points | English 70 points
Overall test targets
Math
Japanese
Science
Social
Studies
-
Workbook
Vocabulary
Grammar
Reading
comprehension
One page per day
-
8/24
7th grade chemistry review sheet
8/25
7th grade biology review sheet
8/26
7th grade geology review sheet
8/27
7th grade physics review sheet
8/28
8th grade chemistry review sheet
8/29
8th grade biology review sheet
8/30
8th grade geology review sheet
8/31
8th grade physics review sheet
Geo-
graphy
review
sheet
His-
tory
review
sheet
First
sem-
ester
review
sheet
For math, the most important thing
is to enjoy solving problems.
Start with some easy ones.
No can do. My head...
L-Let's try something a little easier!
All right, I did it!
Well? Did I get it right?
How did you suddenly get an answer halfway through?
It just came to me!
I had a hunch!
It's wrong!
And you have to show your work
to get full credit, you know.
That's odd.
Is this from elementary school?
Yes.
It's from when we went on that school trip.
Sure brings back memories.
The curry was so good...
You've been friends since elementary school, haven't you?
Yes, we've been friends since forever ago.
Aren't we kind of stuck with each other?
By the way, where's Isa-nee?
She said she's been busy with her modeling work lately...
Go, go!
Get him!
Is it around here?
It's a tie.
Four wins, four losses, one tie.
Aya-chan!
Hey!
Come to think of it, this is my first time at Youko's place.
Oh yeah, Aya...
I-I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Anyway, Aya. Decide on a first-choice school yet?
Well, for now I'm going with the one from before.
The wonderful rich-girl school?
Yeah, Suiren Girls' Academy.
I mean, my parents and teachers did say I should go there.
I see.
And here I thought we could go to the same school again...
Hey, don't get cocky.
We still don't know if we'll get in.
No, I'm sure we will!
Aya-chan's helping us study, after all.
Isn't that right?
Oh, of course!
Are your own studies coming along okay, Aya?
N-Naturally.
Unlike you two, I have a steady study regimen.
Ouch.
Thanks for helping us out!
Worry less about me and more about yourselves.
All right, break over.
Aw! Wasn't that a little short?
Youko, it looks like you're in good shape.
Yes!
But Shino...
The second semester's only just begun!
It's too early to give up!
Yeah, there's still a ways to go!
Yes...
Hello, hellower, hellorist...
Done already?
Yes, please give me the next set!
You're amazing! You did all of that in one night?
I'm not amazing at all. I just have to work twice as hard as everyone else.
Aya-chan, you're probably busy with
studying for your own exams, but...
It's fine.
Teaching you two has made my grades go up too.
Shino, I'm going to ramp up the intensity, so brace yourself!
Once I'm through with you, your hair
could very well have turned gray!
What do you mean?
Is it going to catch fire?
C-Could you at least make it blonde?
Ema
Blonde hair!
the test !!
Pass the exam
with everyone!
Make it so
Blonde hair!
Let's all pass
the test !!
Pass the exam
with everyone!
Inokuma Youko
Make it so
I'll definitely pass the test!!!
Blonde hair!
Let's all pass
the test !!
Komichi Aya
Pass the exam
with everyone!
Inokuma Youko
Make it so
I'll definitely pass the test!!!
Blonde hair!
Let's all pass
the test !!
Komichi Aya
Pass the exam
with everyone!
Inokuma Youko
Make it so
I'll definitely pass the test!!!
Oomiya Shinobu
Blonde hair!
Let's all pass
the test !!
Blonde hair!
Komichi Aya
Pass the exam
with everyone!
Inokuma Youko
Make it so
I'll definitely pass the test!!!
Oomiya Shinobu
Blonde hair!
Let's all pass
the test !!
Blonde hair!
Komichi Aya
Pass the exam
with everyone!
Inokuma Youko
Make it so
I'll definitely pass the test!!!
Oomiya Shinobu
Blonde hair!
Let's all pass
That warmed me up!
It's delicious!
It's almost time.
Yeah.
Aya-chan, Youko-chan.
Let's have another good year.
Yeah, same!
Aya.
Aya-chan.
Shino.
Youko.
How did Suiren Girls' Academy turn out?
Thanks for asking. I got in.
Congratulations, Aya-chan!
That's great! I thought you failed by the look on your face!
You did it, Aya!
Youko...
Aya-chan, you're going to be at a faraway school in the spring.
And here I thought we could've
gone to the same school...
Hey, Shino.
I-I'm sorry.
These are tears of joy.
I'm not sad because you're going far away or anything...
Shino?
Come on, you're just making it hard for Aya.
Really, I'm happy for you!
I don't want you to feel bad.
Just congratulate her and leave it at that.
You're right. Congratulations.
Yeah. Thanks, both of you.
Geez, tomorrow's the big day, you know?
You'll catch a cold.
Heavy...
Hang in there.
[Train delay announcement] Due to the snow, the train schedule will be
Today, of all days?!
Will we make it?
[Train delay announcement] Due to the snow, the train schedule will be
There's still plenty of time!
The ground's slippery, so please don't run!
There are girls from lots of middle schools here.
I wonder if any of them will be our friends one day.
We'll need to get in first.
That's right.
Looks like somehow...
...we made it in time.
Oh? It's those girls.
Hang in there.
Exam Area
This Way
Huh? Aya?
Aya-chan?
What are you doing here?
Exam Area
This Way
Aya-chan!
Exam Area
This Way
Why are you here?
I-I'm taking it too.
Huh? But you already got into Suiren.
I sent an application here too, so...
Tell us earlier!
I feel so reassured!
Seeing Aya-chan's face made me feel a lot less nervous.
Yeah!
Now, begin.
Who were the border merchants who caused culture to flourish, as in (E)?
Which emperor built the temple as seen in (F)?
What country, referred to in (G) was granted trading rights at the island of Dejima
near Nagasaki by the shogunate at the beginning of the 19th century?
Who was the author of (H), "The Book of the Marvels of the World"?
Answer the following questions:
What were the samurai who entered the shogun's retinue called?
This is harder than I thought it'd be.
Will they be okay?
That's right, they worked really hard for this.
You've done all you could. I'm sure it'll be fine.
I feel like it was really hard.
Youko-chan, when's the deadline for the fallback applications again?
No idea.
But we should probably look it up.
Come on!
Now that the test's over, let's go treat ourselves!
Treat ourselves?
Okay!
Y-Yeah!
Moegi High School Entrance Exam Results
I can't, Youko-chan!
Check for me!
I-I can't do it either! Aya, please!
Mine too, please!
Geez...
Come on, look.
See for yourself.
It's there!
We're up there!
We did it! We did it, Aya!
It's my number!
Kuzehashi-sensei?
Have you gotten used to seeing these things unfold yet?
Not yet.
Some here passed, but others did not.
Frankly, I don't know how I should feel.
True.
But whether they're crying or smiling,
this is a very important moment in their lives.
Moegi High School Entrance Exam Results
School uniforms
Western-style apparel
Masuya
Um, Mom!
Over here, girls!
So we're finally saying goodbye to Aya.
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Don't forget to write us!
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Well, her house is still nearby, so we can see her during breaks.
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Party
Middle School Graduation & Aya-chan Farewell
Aya-chan
Thank You
Um...
Today's Star
There's something I need to tell you.
Don't say a thing!
Today's Star
I don't need words to know how you feel!
We'll always be together!
Th-That's not what I mean...
Um...
Don't make me cry any more!
H-Hey!
We'll send you letters with express mail!
Let's just enjoy today to the bitter end!
Oomiya
Okay then.
You look good in that uniform, Shinobu.
Have a nice day.
Thanks! I'm off now!
Morning, Shino.
Good morning, Youko-chan.
You feel like a completely different person with that uniform on.
And you feel like a real older sister suddenly, Youko-chan!
Moegi High School
Entrance Ceremony
We're finally high schoolers.
It's pretty exciting.
Youko-chan.
Let's do it.
One, two!
Shino! Youko!
Aya-chan!
Why are you here?
What about Suiren Girls' Academy?
I ended up coming here.
Coming here? You mean...
Sorry I didn't tell you.
I just couldn't get it out.
But you got into your first-choice school.
And didn't you talk with your parents and teachers?
I did. And I told them.
My first-choice school was this one.
Entrance Ceremony
Moegi High School
Besides, I don't know what you two'd do without me!
Aya...
Aya-chan...
Aya-chan, Youko-chan!
Let's have another great three years!
Sounds great, Shino! Aya!
Let's go then, Youko-chan, Aya-chan.
Okay!
One, two!
And they lived happily ever after.
Without Aya, Shino and I would've probably ended up in a different uniform.
I'm so glad everyone managed to pass!
All thanks to the amazing Ayaya.
Thanks so much for that, Aya!
P-Please, that was so long ago...
I really respect you!
Thank you, Aya!
I'm grateful too!
I didn't do anything...
Shino deserves the credit for her hard work.
Wait, what about me?
We've returned!
Welcome back, Shino!
Present! I mean, what did you buy?
Actually, you see...
I brought all of you presents to express
my thanks for what you do every day!
All of us?
Wow! I can't believe it!
Now, extend your hands and close your eyes.
Excited
Us too?
This is kind of embarrassing.
All right, you can open your eyes now.
I couldn't think of anything you'd have all liked.
But there are some things money can't buy!
What I gave you was the gift of friendship!
I molded my hopes that we'd continue to be friends into a heart!
This... This means...
Karen!
You're moved to tears!
Thank you, Shino.
Same from me! Thanks for everything you do!
Good grief.
Okay now, I brought you something too.
Roll cakes!
I had some with a friend a while ago,
and they were really good.
I got black tea too.
Wow! Super surprise!
Thank you, Isami!
This feels like déjà vu...
Autumn Festival
Zombie Café
Theater Performances
Youko!
Sorry, sorry!
Hurry!
Coming right now!
Takoyaki
It's finally time for Shino's play!
They worked so hard on it!
I'm going to support them with all I've got!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
shibaraku buri da ne
Me too!
The rain has dried
ameagari de
I won't let you show me up!
and the skies have cooled
suzushiku natta kono sora ni
Karasu-chan, when did you get here?
I can't wait!
This is the landscape I once saw with you
kimi to itsuka mita keshiki
You're having too much fun.
Class 2-A's play,
"Your Hair is Gold", will begin shortly.
As the days go by
tsukihi no nagare ni
everything
nani mo ka mo ga
changes a little
katachi wo kaeteyuku kedo
But I believe
shinjiau
That title's very much like Shino.
that this feeling is different
kono kimochi dake wa
and won't ever change
kawaranai itsumademo
With brilliant smiles
tobikiri no egao de
Aya?!
we changed the world
sekai wo kaeta
Several hours earlier
And you, with your reassuring gaze
kimi wa sukitooru manazashi de
Several hours earlier
Your Hair Is
Let's give it our all
Today's the day.
We've done everything we could.
filled with so much courage
mune ni kakaekirenai hodo no
Let's show them what we've got.
You've gotten really good at acting.
that it spilled over
yuuki wo kureta ne
It's thanks to Ayaya's intense acting training!
Always be my shining star
Not like that, like this!
Follow the script!
Aya-chan, this play would've been even better with you in an acting role!
Even when we're far apart
hanarebanare de mo
Really? How unfortunate.
Smug
we understand each other
wakariaeru
I'd have liked Youko to see me too.
When I'm trying to hold back tears
namida koraeru toki mo
This is bad!
Our princess actress came down with a cold!
your words echo in my ears
kimi no kotoba ga kodama suru
We knew that what this world needed
kono sekai wo mitashiteru no wa
We need a substitute!
Aya-chan, this is your chance to shine!
was a bit of rejoicing
yorokobi dake nanda to shitte
And I believe that with that,
shinjiau sono kimochi dake de
I'm sorry! I can't do it after all!
Aya-chan! Aya-chan!
In our elementary school play,
I got so nervous I fainted!
we'd be flooded in happiness
shiawase ni tsutsumareru
You'll be fine!
With pure white hearts
-
masshiro na kokoro de
Put this on!
we made our dream came true
yume wo kanaeta
What is this?!
And you, with your inexhaustible kindness
kimi wa tsuki mo senu yasashisa to
It eases your nerves and gives you courage!
and your almost annoying earnestness
-
akireru hodo no hitamukisa de
Really, it works!
brought me to this future
mirai wo kureta ne
That only works on you!
It's dazzling
me kurumeku
Apologies.
I shouldn't force you to do this.
In a distant memory
tooku kioku ni
I'll do it myself, then!
lies a smile forged from sunlight
mabayui bakari afureru egao
Shinobu-chan, you need to give backstage directions!
that I'll never forget
wasurerarenu
Oh, right. Isn't there anyone who can play the role?
My memories will be dyed
-
omoide dake kimi iro ni
Shino's been working so hard for this.
by you
somatteru
I want to help make it a success!
All right. I'll play the princess!
Are you sure, Aya-chan?
Leave it to me!
I'll show you all!
Who might you be?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
shibaraku buri da ne
Still, it's scary!
The rain has dried
ameagari de
If only I had a mask...
and the skies have cooled
suzushiku natta kono sora ni
Aya!
Do your best!
We're cheering for you!
This is the landscape I once saw with you
kimi to itsuka mita keshiki
Alice! Youko!
As the days go by
tsukihi no nagare ni
I-I didn't ask you to come see me or anything!
everything
nani mo ka mo ga
changes a little
katachi wo kaeteyuku kedo
But I believe
shinjiau
Forget about that! Say your lines!
that this feeling is different
kono kimochi dake wa
But I think I'm a little less tense now.
and won't ever change
kawaranai itsumademo
The little birds are singing!
With brilliant smiles
tobikiri no egao de
What a wonderful day it is today!
we changed the world
sekai wo kaeta
And you, with your reassuring gaze
kimi wa sukitooru manazashi de
Aya, amazing! What stage presence!
She's...
filled with so much courage
mune ni kakaekirenai hodo no
She's good?
Who is it?
Who is behind that bush?
that it spilled over
yuuki wo kureta ne
Always be my shining star
I'm Irene, the princess of this country.
What is your name?
I-I...
Flap
Don't tell me...
After all that practice...
Even when we're far apart
hanarebanare de mo
You forgot?
I forgot.
we understand each other
wakariaeru
But I have to do something, or Shino's play will be ruined.
When I'm trying to hold back tears
namida koraeru toki mo
No problem!
your words echo in my ears
kimi no kotoba ga kodama suru
I-I'm pretending to be a goldfish!
You don't need to ad-lib!
We knew that what this world needed
kono sekai wo mitashiteru no wa
That's right.
I can ad-lib through this.
was a bit of rejoicing
yorokobi dake nanda to shitte
You are Irene, you say?
And I believe that with that,
shinjiau sono kimochi dake de
I'm a spy from another land.
Those lines...
we'd be flooded in happiness
shiawase ni tsutsumareru
Japanese ninja!
I'm a kunoichi!
With pure white hearts
-
masshiro na kokoro de
we made our dream came true
yume wo kanaeta
Secret technique: Quick Clothes Change!
And you, with your inexhaustible kindness
kimi wa tsuki mo senu yasashisa to
This play's set in Medieval Europe, you know!
Karen-chan's ad-libbing...
Your Hair Is
and your almost annoying earnestness
-
akireru hodo no hitamukisa de
Your Hair Is
That's a cosplay from the anime Nin-Nin Kunoichi Ooichi!
brought me to this future
mirai wo kureta ne
I wasn't prepared for something like this.
It's dazzling
me kurumeku
Your Hair Is
Your
Hair
Is
Your
Hair
Is
Your
Hair
Is
What do we do about the next part?
Your
Hair
Is
In a distant memory
tooku kioku ni
Shinobu-chan!
I want to make this a success for everyone's sake.
lies a smile forged from sunlight
mabayui bakari afureru egao
I'll improvise and figure something out!
that I'll never forget
wasurerarenu
My memories will be dyed
-
omoide dake kimi iro ni
Everyone, lend me your power!
by you
somatteru
Shinobu-chan's in serious mode?
The blonde is blinding!
Hey, want to make a guest appearance?
I'll help! I used to be in the drama club, you know.
Nin-nin!
Where do we go from here?
Good afternoon!
Yes, when I'm with you
sou kimi to ireba
We're the totem pole fairies!
I can always be honest
itsudatte sunao ni nareru
pit pat
Karasuma-sensei!
Worry not, Princess Irene!
We're looking after you!
With brilliant smiles
tobikiri no egao de
There are lots of people hiding all around you.
we changed the world
sekai wo kaeta
And you, with your reassuring gaze
kimi wa sukitooru manazashi de
Play along.
quietly took my hands
shizuka ni ryoute wo nigirishimete
Wh-What's going on?
and put on a smile
hohoemi ukabeta
Look over there.
With pure white smiles
-
masshiro na kokoro de
Shino!
we made our dream come true
yume wo kanaeta
Shino's improvising an entirely new story.
And you, in my dreams
kimi wa watashi no yume no naka de
Blonde power!
So just go with what everyone's doing.
will continue to shine
zutto kiramekitsudzukeru
now, and for all time
ima mo kore kara saki mo
Yes!
You've always been my idol
itsumademo kimi wa akogare no hito
Always be my shining star
Shino.
Yes?
I'm really happy I decided to go to this school.
Same here!
Komichi Aya
You've always been by me, smiling
itsumo tonari de waratteta yo ne
Karen
Alice
Shino
I love you all
minna no koto ga daisuki dakara
so my wish is a modest one
sasayaka na negai mitsuketa
"Let these happy times last forever"
zutto shiawase na jikan wo
I'd never noticed, but we'd been together for forever
kidzukeba itsumo issho ni ita ne
Pass the exam
with everyone!
Inokuma Youko
Make it so
I'll definitely pass the test!!!
Blonde hair!
Let's all pass
the test !!
Komichi Aya
Pass the exam
with everyone!
Inokuma Youko
Make it so
I'll definitely pass the test!!!
Blonde hair!
Let's all pass
Komichi Aya
Pass the exam
with everyone!
Inokuma Youko
Make it so
I'll definitely pass the test!!!
Oomiya Shinobu
Blonde hair!
Let's all pass
the test !!
Blonde hair!
Komichi Aya
Pass the exam
with everyone!
Inokuma Youko
Make it so
I'll definitely pass the test!!!
Oomiya Shinobu
Blonde hair!
Let's all pass
the test !!
Blonde hair!
Komichi Aya
Pass the exam
with everyone!
Inokuma Youko
Make it so
I'll definitely pass the test!!!
Oomiya Shinobu
Let's all pass
Blonde hair!
It became just another part of everyday life
sore ga futsuu da to omotteita
This strange feeling is a wonderful thing
fushigi na kibun kokochi ii kara
so it's become very important to me
taisetsu na basho ni natteitanda
It wasn't pure chance
guuzen ja nai
that we met
watashitachi nara
We were drawn together by a special force
inryoku de hikiyoseatta
I'll say "do your best"
"ganbatte!" iu yo
with all my heart
negai komete
since I want to keep walking with you all
minna de issho ni aruiteikitai kara
One step at a time
ippotsudzu de
is fast enough for me
ii kara zutto ne
I want to keep supporting you
ouen shiteitainda yo
Starlight
Geez, Karen!
That could've gone all sorts of wrong!
Sorry!
Don't be. In the end,
you made the play even better!
Hello, hellower, hellorist
Shino!
We met in spring amidst
raining cherry blossoms
sakura maichiru haru deatte
It all turned out all right!
I'm just glad we somehow ended up with a proper play.
and we spent a
sun-scorched summer together
taiyou mabushii natsu sugi
It was Shino who carried the day.
followed by an autumn
of skies stained red
akaku irodzuku aki no sora to
Good job.
Shino, you're awesome!
No, it was thanks to
everyone and the blonde hair.
Blush
and a winter of white snow
shiroi yuki ga furu fuyu koete
Blush
She's right.
Shinobu-chan,
you were amazing with the wig on.
these days passed in a flash
atto iu ma ni sugiru mainichi
It was the hair that did the trick!
I knew it worked on Shino!
Yeah!
but I still haven't had enough
demo madamada tarinai yo
Thank you, blonde hair!
Give Shino the credit,
not the hair!
Heart of Japan
Heart of Wa
No matter the circumstances
donna toki mo
issho ni kimetai
let's decide together
Boar
Pupu
what path we'll take together
sou yatte erandekita kono michi wa
Blonde power!!!
Blonde hair
The one miracle we've encountered
tatta hitotsu mitsuketa kiseki
Boar
I want to forever believe that this was it
zutto "koko da" tte shinjiteitai
Shino
gulp gulp!!
Kokeshi
Pharma
Power
It's delicious!!
My present is love,
it's proof of our friendship!!!
There!!
We've come all this way, saying "do your best"
"ganbatte" zutto aruitekita
Al
ways
smil
ing
trying not to let the stars outshine us
hoshi no hikari ni mo makenai you ni
I'm so glaaaad
This place is special
kono basho ga taisetsu dakara
so I'll make a wish with all my heart
motto tsuyoku negau yo
Starlight
To the new students: Congratulations on your enrollment.
Moegi High School
Entrance Ceremony Location
Entrance Ceremony
Starting today, you will be students of Moegi High School...
It's hard to believe we're in the same class again.
This is the power of friendship!
Hey, stop whispering.
We got yelled at.
I've been thinking about some things these days.
Aya-chan!
Want to go visit Class C together?
Sure.
Even if we haven't been friends since childhood,
even if I don't have blonde hair,
I'm coming too!
Shino and I are friends.
Now,
and forever.