Smiling is so hard.
No, really, it's totally true!
What, seriously?
Bright and chipper this morning, huh?
G-Good morning!
Good... morning...
One look from me is enough to scare them stiff...
Kuzehashi-sensei!
Good marning!
Kujou-san, good—
Sensei, can I borrow your scrunchie?
Scrunchie! Your scrunchie!
Hurry! Hurry up!
H-Here.
Thanks muchly!
Behold!
What?
Wh-What are you doing?
We're...
playing color tag!
Give that back.
Put on a winning smile
zettai egao de
We have heaps of dreams to dream
mada mada ippai yume miyou
Whether it's "We always have fun",
itsumo tanoshii ne tte
or "See you tomorrow, I've gotta run",
mata ashita jaa ne tte
being with you all puts a smile on my face
waraiaeru hora minna ga iru kara
One small step in my usual way
okiniiri no step
with a special jump just for today
kyou wa tokubetsu jump
and already I can see the end of the race
te wo nobaseba sugu todoku basho nan da
About to be late
Every single one of our days
kirakira tte kagayaku no
has oodles of brilliance in store
watashitachi no mainichi
Just use the secret phrase
himitsu no angou de hora
to open another door
mata tobira akeyou
Good day, just remember
Good day kokoro wo
to let your heart fly free sometimes
tokidoki zettai tanoshinjaou
The dream we're living will grow again
kyou mo fukuramu yume ga
It's all etched into the skies around us
ooki na sora ni hikaru yo
I've got your hands in mine
gyutte tsunaida
and I'm never letting go
ryoute wo zettai hanasanai kara
Until we're the stars of this dream
yume ni kagayakeru made
let's run forward, brimming with smiles
hajikeru egao de susumou
Yes!
Let's go!
Let's get going!
icchaou
Present For You
Kujou-san's friendliness is a virtue,
but she needs to learn some restraint.
Good morning, Kuzehashi-sensei.
Good morning.
U-Um, Karasuma-sensei...
This is for you. Please take it.
Can I really?
Glee
It's so cute!
Thank you very much.
It's so soft!
I actually have a favor to ask of you.
Cuddle, cuddle... You're so cuddly.
Please teach me how to grasp hold of people's hearts!
How are you so cuddly?
What?
You just nailed it...
So cuddly...
What?
I see.
You want your students to stop fearing you, right?
Yes.
Don't worry about it!
You're admirable just the way you are.
No, now that a new year has begun,
I'm trying to become a new person.
This year, I want my students to like me.
That's Matsubara-san and
Higurashi-san from my class.
The morning assembly's about to start...
Be sure to pat it a few times.
Again? Why?
Sensei?
I'll collect your career surveys now.
Please pass your forms forward.
I wonder if it looked like I was glaring at them.
Maybe I should try sunglasses...
No, that would be even scarier.
What a bright smile, Kujou-san!
I need to respond somehow...
Has Karen done something again?
I did it again...
Gloomy this early?
Sensei...
When you're feeling down,
you should squeeze something cute.
Something cute?
Karasuma-sensei, you forgot something.
Oh, thank you, Alice-san.
Do you have a moment?
Huh?
Squeeze!
What?
She just moved in and did it!
Lucky
Is she a god?
Welcome back.
What's wrong, Alice?
Karasuma-sensei squeezed me.
Oh, did she now?
Squeeze!
Why would you do that?
Just because.
Just because?!
Alice!
Alice is so cute when she's flustered.
Go for it, Ayaya!
Squeeze... squeeze...
Youko, please!
You too, Aya?
Shino, I finally get to see you!
Alice!
We've only had the morning assembly so far.
Want to come to the library, Youko?
We're just going to return some books.
Sure.
Library
Blonde hair...
Washing that must be a real headache.
Karen, are you familiar with the
Japanese expression "grinding sesame"?
Japanese Dictionary
It means humoring someone so they'll like you.
Yes, just like that.
Sesame garnish, sesame sauce, sesame ice cream.
Japanese people love sesame.
And it's good for you, too.
Sesame, huh?
I see you're both studying hard.
By the way Karen, you've been trying to become
friends with Kuzehashi-sensei recently, haven't you?
Yeah. I want to be friends with her.
I know!
Since Japanese people love it so much,
I'll give her some sesame!
She'll love it!
You're really grinding that sesame!
Roasted Sesame
This is for you. Please enjoy!
Sesame...
Th-Thank you very much, Kujou-san...
Have some coffee.
Karasuma-sensei.
Yes?
I don't understand my students.
I'm holding a tea party at my house next weekend!
A party?
It's for afternoon tea.
Shino's really into it right now.
Afternoon tea is a tea party held
around four in the afternoon.
English noblewomen began holding afternoon tea parties in the mid-19th century as social events.
Tea is very English.
Aren't you a little late to the party?
I actually didn't realize black tea was so popular.
Because...
Alice never drinks it!
Fuuu~
Nothing beats green tea.
I like black tea too.
Is tea all you have during afternoon tea?
Youko...
I mean, I was hoping you'd have some snacks.
Of course!
But I want to make it a proper tea party.
What are we going to do?
We're going to make sweets!
Sounds nice. You can't have tea without scones.
Ooh, me! I want cookies!
Let's make some of those too.
Alright! I'm so excited!
You're going to make both?
Will you be okay? Isn't that a bit too greedy?
Rumble
You should listen to your desires!
I'm putting my life on the line for this tea party!
Why would you go that far?
Rumble
Smells nice.
Sesame is delicious, isn't it?
Ground sesame is even tastier.
I agree.
It has more calories than
roasted sesame, but I prefer it too.
Sensei?
C-Calories?
Coming!
Thank you for coming.
Thanks for inviting us!
Pardon the intrusion.
We already got everything ready.
Okay! Let's get started.
You're baking in those clothes?
They'll get dirty.
A maid must always wear her uniform.
It's okay. I'll be careful.
Told you so.
I'm glad it didn't stain.
Yeah...
Thank you.
Hey, where's Karen?
She said she'd be late.
She's bringing us a cake stand.
Really?
How authentic.
Karen, welcome—
Here I am!
Karen! That's not a cake stand!
That's a food delivery box!
The cake stand was heavy,
so I brought something close.
You put the food in here.
It's not similar!
They're nothing alike!
There, there. It's okay, we still can put stuff in it.
Let's pull ourselves together and make some sweets!
You're the only one with real cooking
experience, so I'm counting on you.
I haven't really baked much before...
I'm counting on you!
We're counting on you!
Stop that! I don't do well under pressure!
I wonder if Kuzehashi-sensei's a good cook.
I bet she's great at it! She's the home ec teacher, after all.
What are you making there?
Onee-chan!
Isa-nee.
We're making cookies and scones.
Do you have the day off?
Yeah.
I know. Why don't we get Isa-nee to help us?
Good idea. I'm a bit uneasy
about doing this by ourselves.
Sure.
Incidentally, my best dish is fried eggs.
Burnt to a crisp.
Never mind, then.
Let me know when they're done.
I'm not great at delicate tasks like these...
Sorry!
You're so clumsy, Youko.
Sorry, Aya. Are you okay?
Jeez, Youko! Just go and sit down! I'll do everything!
Sorry...
Normally, it's the other way around.
The sun is setting. What should we do?
How many hours have we been baking?
It's not really afternoon tea anymore.
What?!
Assam! Darjeeling! Earl Grey!
Shino, calm down!
Pick up the pace, everyone!
We can still make it!
This is one frantic tea party!
There.
Now we just have to cut out the cookies and bake them.
I brought a bunch of cookie cutters.
They're all hearts.
They're cute, but they're all the same.
Karen, yours have sesame in them.
They're sesame cookies.
It's a mass production of hearts...
Hearts...
What's wrong with you?!
It's so boring when they're all the same!
Hurry it up, you two!
They're done!
Hooray!
They look delicious!
Yeah!
They look great!
But it's nighttime...
Pitch Black...
It's all about the spirit of things!
Let's make some tea!
It's time for dinner.
You can have your tea party tomorrow.
The cookies are so crispy.
They're just sweet enough, too.
This isn't the atmosphere I wanted.
You think so?
As long as we're together,
eating anywhere is fun.
Alice...
You're right.
But next time, let's have tea at your place.
What date shall we set?
She's set her mind on it!
Thanks for the food.
You're finished?
Yes.
I'm going to go around and share some.
Here you go!
Thanks for always giving me snacks.
These are all for us?
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Here you go.
For me?
We made these cookies yesterday.
Please share them with the other teachers.
Th-Thank you.
You're welcome!
Sesame
Sesame again?!
Is she trying to tell me something?
I figured it out.
And?
Sesame must be the in-thing for high school girls right now.
Huh?
Keeping up with the latest trends will help you understand your students.
Smug
I see.
That's very instructive!
Sesame!
Open sesame.
Hello, everyone.
Open sesame!
Faculty Office
You're making happi coats in home ec today?
That sounds fun.
Hands-on lessons make me nervous, though.
You'll be okay. With a little spirit, you can get through it.
For example...
Happis make me happy!
You can't fail if you open with that.
B-But...
She's got nothing but spirit...
I'm sure they'll all roar with laughter!
I'm so excited to make happi coats!
Your class has home ec in fifth period today, right?
Yes, and then it's your turn tomorrow.
Yeah! I want to make mine soon!
Aya-chan, you can make them any size you want.
You don't need to take measurements.
I-I know that.
I was just measuring how much
Youko's grown over the last year.
So, what's the result?
It's great that you're so full of energy!
Not sure how you measured that.
I'd rather have a cooking lesson.
I've been into sewing lately,
so I'm happy we're doing this.
You're into a lot of things.
Cute clothes and accessories can be so expensive.
Like this
So I try to make everything I can myself!
That's amazing!
You made this yourself? What an unexpected talent...
It must be because you love foreign stuff.
With this much passion, you might
actually become an interpreter some day.
And at the end of the road, you'll become a world-renowned hero!
What?!
Historical Figure
Shino's amazing!
Sewing Room
It's Karasuma-sensei's advice...
I'll trust her.
Happi... Happy... Happy...
Kuzehashi-sensei!
I'm really excited about today's class!
Happis make me happy!
Just kidding.
Kujou-san!
Wh-Why are you mad at me?!
I'm sorry!
Happi
If you have any questions, just ask.
There are sewing machines in the sewing room,
as well as other dangerous equipment.
I'm sure you know what will happen if you play around.
Okay, begin!
(Translation)
Be careful not to hurt yourselves!
Alone
Come on, ask me anything you'd like.
Sensei.
Yes?
Do you have a question?
I'm finished.
What?
O-Oomiya-san! Is that really you, Oomiya-san?
This is wonderful.
The stitching is extremely precise.
I'm glad you did such a thorough job.
What is it?
I'm happy that you praised me.
Th-That's...
Aya-chan, how's yours coming?
It keeps going off center.
You need to go faster.
B-But...
I'm afraid of the needle!
It's okay.
It's okay!
Imagine you're jumping off the platform at Kiyomizu!
It takes that much resolve?!
Take a ten-minute break.
Another hour, huh?
Kujou-san is working during break time...
Karen, what are you making?
I'm making a doll out of my leftover cloth.
Is it for the girl in Class C?
Alice, what's that on your head?
A bridal veil! Shino made it for me.
She said I look good in white, so she wants to make a wedding dress for me someday.
Really?
In Japan, they say that if you wear a wedding dress before the big day, you'll delay your own wedding.
Do they say that abroad too?
What? You don't want it?
But it looks so good on you...
Happi
Continued
Kujou-san.
Yes?
If you have any questions, you can ask me.
Thank you.
But...
Enter
Karen
Shino helped me finish mine.
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
I'm finished too!
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
Enter
Karen
Sun
These words you stitched on...
...express our individuality!
Sun
If you didn't finish your happi today,
have it done by our next class.
Goodbye.
Today didn't go so well, either.
Kuzehashi-sensei!
I made this for you!
You made this during break...
Kujou-san, you keep giving me gifts.
Is there something you want from me?
You have a beautiful smile.
What?
I want to see you smile more.
Kujou-san...
Am I imagining things? There's this weird image...
I accept your gift.
Okay.
Thank you.
Faculty Office
Excuse me.
Thanks for waiting.
Everyone's waiting at the entrance.
Goodbye, Karasu-chan and Kusshi-chan.
You're being too familiar with the teachers!
I prefer calling people by nicknames.
As long as you're sensible about
the timing, I don't care what you call me.
Kuzehashi-sensei!
See you tomorrow.
Kusshi sounds a bit like cookie, doesn't it?
Which is fine. It's easy to say, and you can't choose your own nickname anyway...
Hey! What is it, Sensei?
I'm sorry...
I-I'm not saying...
Good morning.
Kuzehashi-sensei's been more
cheerful and easier to talk to lately.
She's so cute when she smiles.
I understand Kuzehashi-sensei a little better now.
Same!
She's every bit as nice as Karasuma-sensei.
I'm glad everyone finally realized it.
Smug
Why do you sound so smug?
Sensei and I are best buddies.
I can even dance with her.
Maybe you shouldn't...
Just you watch!
Kuzehashi-sensei!
Let's dance!
What?
Anyway, did you do your homework?
What? Um...
You did do your homework, didn't you?
Hold it!
Are they really friends?
They say you grow fonder of students the more trouble they give you.
You won't get away with this!
I'm sorry!
Sorry isn't good enough!
When I close my eyes, I can almost hear the melody of your song
hitomi tojireba kimi no utau melody kikoeru hazu
On a sun-speckled field
komorebi no yureru shibafu ni
I spot a familiar head of hair
tatazumu ushirogami ga nabiku
You're waiting at the usual spot
itsumo to kawaranai kono basho de
smiling and waving at me
hohoende te wo furu kimi ga iru
The unexciting lay of our town
minareta kono machinami mo
and even the daily breezy sunrises
asayake ni nagareteku kaze mo
somehow take on a different luster
kimi ga soba ni iru tada sore dake de
when you're with me
mabushii kirameki ni kawaru
Whenever I stare deep into your eyes
itsu no hi mo kimi wa hitomi no oku ni
I see nothing but pure happiness
yorokobi afureru
Things like the sunny sky that day
ano hareta sora mo
and each shining day of our lives
kagayaku hibi mo
should be treasured
watashitachi no takaramono
We can spend the rest of time
haruka na ashita wo
chasing after tomorrow
mitsumeta mama de
nestled up together
yorisoeru itsumademo
When I close my eyes, the melody of your song comes flooding in
hitomi tojireba kimi no utau melody wasurenai yo
I'll never forget it
itsumade de mo
'cause you're my best friend
If she were an animal...
Karen-san would be a cat.
Komichi-san would be a black bunny rabbit.
Karasu-chan, what would I be?
Inokuma-san, you'd be...
Since you eat everything in sight, you'd be...
Vrooo
a vacuum cleaner.
At least pick an actual animal!
Vrooo
I see it.
Karasu-chan, don't agree with her!
Ballroom
Dancing
Kujou-san invited me to dance with her...
Studying
Oh my...
Ballroom
Dancing
Studying
Ballroom
Dancing
1 Week Later
We can dance now.
What are you talking about?
1 Week Later
Forgot
That's not how the steps go!
It's like this!
No!
She's so serious.
See you!
You're So Bright
Wait!