tobira hirakeba nejireta hiru no yoru
Behind the door lies the twisted night of a twisted day
kinou dou yatte kaetta? karada dake ga tashika
How did I get home last night? My own body's all I'm sure of
ohayou kore kara mata maigo no tsuzuki
I'll be off again tomorrow, losing myself as always
minareta shiranai keshiki no naka de
in this familiar but alien scenery
mou dame tte omotte kara wari to nandaka yareteru
Once I thought I was done for, things started working out
shinikiranai kurai ni joubu nanka chotto hazukashii
It seems like death won't touch me, it's a bit embarrassing really
yarubeki koto wa wasuretete mo wakaru
I couldn't forget my duty even if I wanted to
sou shinai to totemo kurushii kara
This pain serves as a constant reminder
kao wo agete kuroi me no hito
I look up into your large, dark eyes
kimi ga mita kara hikari wa umareta
and you become my leading light
eranda iro de nutta sekai ni kakomarete
When the whole world is painted the colors you chose,
erabenai kizu no imi wa doko darou
do the scars inflicted by others hold any meaning?
gojibun dake ga hero sekai no mannaka de
I'm the only hero in this story
owaru made dezuppari stage no ue
I have to stay on stage until the curtain falls
doushiyou karappo no furi mo dekinai
What should I do? I can't pretend to be hollow anymore
hello doumo boku wa koko
Hello world, here I am