I've gotten used to this cataclysmic competition
choutenpenchii mitai na kyousou ni mo narete
I sometimes mistake these insane days for peace
konna nichijou wo heiwa to mimachigau
As I'm jolted around by this crazy roller coaster
ranburin kosuta yusaburenagara
I wonder what it was I had to keep my sight set on
miushinaenai mono wa nan da
Fundamental equalism became the norm for me
byoudousei genrishugi no gainen ni nomarete
Down to my heart, nothing really matters
kokoro made ga maru de etosetora
Love or hate, I've got to spell it out
daikirai daisuki chanto shaberanakya
Or else I'd be no better than a puppet
ningyou to sashite kawaranai shi
For the people who stroll the city at night,
yo ni machi wo yuku hito dake ni
sometimes happy, sometimes lonely,
ureshisou dattari sabishisou dattari
the contrast dances around the score
kontorasuto ga gosenpu wo tobimawari
and turns into rhythm and music
uta to rizumu ni naru
Marmalade sugar song
mamaredo no shugasongu
Peanuts and bitter step
pinatsu ando bitasuteppu
Sometimes sweet, sometimes bitter, it makes your head spin
amakute nigakute me ga mawarisou desu
Let's keep partying, headed for south-southwest
nannansei wo mezashite paati wo tsuzukeyou
We'll make this a night the whole world will remember
sekaijuu wo odorokasete shimau yoru ni naru
I feel great! Reflect that smile around like a chain reaction
i feel joujou rensa ni natte rifurekuto
Marmalade sugar song
mamaredo no shugasongu
Peanuts and bitter step
pinatsu ando bitasuteppu
Sometimes sweet, sometimes bitter, it makes your head spin
amakute nigakute me ga mawarisou desu
Let's keep partying, headed for south-southwest
nannansei wo mezashite paati wo tsuzukeyou
We'll make this a night the whole world will remember
sekaijuu wo odorokasete shimau yoru ni naru
I feel great! Reflect that smile around like a chain reaction
i feel joujou rensa ni natte rifurekushon
Come on! Jump outta the frying pan, into the fire, and back into the pan again!
douzo ikkyou satte ichinan satte mata ikkyou