douka please can you keep my secret?
Please, please can you keep my secret?
どうか please can you keep my secret?
Kaichou wa Maid-sama!
kira kira to kagayaku miraa
The mirror, shining so brilliantly
キラキラと輝くミラー
watashi wa donna fuu ni utsutteiru no
I wonder how do I look in it
私はどんなふうに映っているの
hora hora to temaneku mirai
The future, beckoning me forward
ホラホラと手招く未来
kore kara donna koto ga okoru no
What will happen from now, I wonder?
これからどんなことが起こるの
me ni mieteiru mono ga subete dewa nai kara
Because what we see is not everything
目に見えているものが全てではないから
mugamuchuu da that's all right
I'm losing myself but that's all right
無我夢中だ that's all right
mayowanaide I will now try
I will now try not to waver
迷わないで I will now try
jibun no kimochi ni massugu de itai
I want to be true to my heart
自分の気持ちに真っ直ぐでいたい
dakedo hitotsu ya futatsu gurai
But even I have a secret or two
だけど一つや二つぐらい
dare ni mo baretakunai
That I want to keep to myself
誰にもばれたくない
naishotte aru mono dakara
内緒ってあるものだから
mune ga chotto itai my secret
That's why my secret makes my heart aches slightly
胸がちょっと痛い my secret
Once upon a time, there lived
a grandmother and a grandfather.
The weather's great today.
Sakura Baa-san went to
the river to do the laundry.
Yukimura Jii-san went to
the mountain to get firewood...
which was what he was supposed to do,
but instead he was helping with the laundry.
Then all of a sudden, a large
peach came drifting down the river.
What is this!?
Yay, I love peaches!
Granny.
Grandmother and Grandfather
took the peach home and...
Shine.
Tried to eat it.
Right then-
From the peach, came out-
Tada!
Even Peach Boy becomes a Maid
I-I am... will... slay the Oni!
Granny! A person came out of the peach!
It's no time to be eating the peach.
I heard that the Oni are kidnapping young girls; terrifying the villagers.
My, what a fine child we have here.
Those atrocious Oni! Unforgivable!
Calm down, Peach Boy.
Act naturally and you'll be fine.
Naturally
Okay.
Granny. When did you come up with the name?
Well, Grandfather and Grandmother. I'll be off!
You're kinda hot, so take
these with you. It's on me.
Eat a lot of kibi-dango.
Thank you, Grandmother.
Take care!
Good luck!
What was this about?
I don't know. Let's eat the peach.
As such, Peach Boy went to slay the Oni and-
he found Dog, Pheasant, and Monkey.
Why are we putting up with this?
It's your fault, Dog! You got tricked by that guy!
So did you, Monkey!
It's your fault for not noticing, Pheasant!
I told you it was suspicious!
What are you guys doing?
Good Samaritan there!
Please help us!
We're about to get killed
after being tricked by a villain!
Peach Boy saved the three who said
they would do anything if he saved them.
But they tried to snag the kibi-dango from him, so he punished them.
See? That's why I had them tied up.
That's the bad guy!
Who are you?
I'm Usui.
I'm the Ring Master of the Moron Trio Circus.
That
That's our members.
So fishy!
I went and started a circus group, but they're useless, so I was just planning to eat them.
I see.
If you're going to kill them or
food's sake, then I can't stop you.
Please stop!
We've only been practicing, so we ran out of food.
All the "training" was you whipping us!
Now,
who should I start with?
I don't taste good!
He's really tasty!
No, he is!
What are you saying?
You're the yummiest!
Hold on a moment.
Please help us.
Before you get eaten, I want to ask one thing.
Oh, so you won't...
Do you know where the Oni are?
No, we don't.
I see.
Usui, if you can't pick one,
I recommend mixing them in a soup.
I'm off now.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
I don't know where the Oni live, but I do
know a village where Oni appeared recently!
It's a village with many young people, but the
day after the Oni came, all the girls were missing.
Which village is this?
We'll take you there if you save us.
Usui...
Sure.
But instead-
Give me a kibi-dango.
And so the Peach Boy departed to search the Oni with Dog, Monkey, Pheasant, and a sketchy Ring Master of a circus group.
Where's our share of kibi-dango?
I ate them all.
Darn!
But, this is kinda nice.
It's like a party led by a hero out to defeat evil.
Party?
You're nuts! Do you think this
is some kind of fun activity?!
We're not on a field trip!
It's not that kind of "party"!
It means "a group of people that travel together to achieve a common goal"!
So something like that is necessary, eh?
In that case-
We'll be a party that slays Oni!
In short, we're the "Oni Slay Party"!
It's a great name. Any objections?
Good, let's go.
Seika Village
So it's here, huh?
Oni Slay Party
The village where the
Oni kidnapped all the girls.
It's completely tattered.
I don't sense a soul here.
I said that's mine!
You plan on snatching it away from me?!
That was the last one that grew from my farm!
No, it's from my farm!
Um...
Who are you?
It's mine!
That bastard!
What I see here happened because of Oni?
Something stinks.
What's wrong?!
He ran away because of the smell.
Dog has a good sense of smell.
If you can't tolerate that level of smell, I suggest you leave this village now.
What do you mean?
This is no longer a village
any sane human can live in.
Hey! What happened? Are you all right?
Ah, so they're out of the race, too.
Care to explain?!
You see, none of us bathe anymore.
After the girls went missing, laundry
and housekeeping all went downhill.
All the guys are going through
a survival-mode lifestyle.
This is more like a war zone than a village.
The law of the jungle applies here.
But life in survival-mode is pretty fun.
It's really thrilling.
What are you going to do with the
village like this when the girls come back?!
They won't.
I mean, we're talking about Oni.
There's no way we can win.
Yeah.
Cut that crap!
We'll go save the girls,
so tell me where the Oni are!
Meanwhile, Yukimura Jii-san and Sakura Baa-san were...
It's so peaceful.
So the Oni Island is beyond this ocean.
I can only see the horizon.
Can we trust those villagers?
They sounded so irresponsible!
They had no intention of helping us out!
It totally looked like we were bothering them.
Let's not do this!
We shouldn't go today!
We might get different
information from another village.
Okay.
Bon voyage!
He doesn't listen to us...
What is this turtle?
Let's flip it on its back.
Do it, do it!
Hey, you guys.
What are you doing?
He saved the turtle.
Could this lead to...
Lead to?
I've heard of a story that goes like this:
If you save a turtle, to show its gratitude, it puts you on its shell and takes you to the palace under the ocean.
Palace? What's this place like?
The sexy Otohime-sama will serve you with plenty of seafood
like sea bream and tuna, and will even give you a souvenir to go.
Big Catch - Warm Welcome
Seriously? Let's have it take us there.
But you must be careful of the
box she gives you as a souvenir.
When you open it, smoke will come out
and you will turn into an old man in no time.
Why does she give out such a dangerous object?
Is the turtle trying to repay
kindness with ingratitude?
Wait. Should we just leave that box unopened?
Precisely.
If we don't open the box, we get to feast out
and have fun with the hot and sexy Otohime-sama.
You guys. Why are you talking so secretively?
Yikes!
N-Nothing!
We'll go to Oni Island on this turtle's back.
We'll lead the way and check things out.
See you later!
Isn't this about to turn into a separate story?
I think it'll be fine.
I can't breathe!
Was it trying to kill us?
I can't swim!
Will we be fine with this puny boat?
What are we going to do if we get stranded? We don't even have any food.
If that happens, we'll eat you guys.
We knew it!
Pheasant! You go find the Oni Island from the sky!
Roger!
We can't see any land...
Pheasant isn't returning.
He probably ran away.
Our bond is tight!
You guys were offering each other
when you were about to get eaten.
This can't be happening...
No way...
How could he run away alone...
I'm hungry...
Me too...
Look, I had one left.
Kibi-Dango
It's mine!
Give it to me!
Get off!
Did you guys drop this normal kibi-dango?
Or is it this stack of postcards that could win you a year's worth of kibi-dango?
Or, is it this postcard that could win you the Hokkaido Sea Food Set
that gives you king crab, sea urchin, salmon roe, and scallops?
Um, that normal kibi-dango.
I see. You're an honest man.
As a prize, I'll give you this postcard
that could win you the Hokkaido Sea Food Set.
Where's the postbox?
There's one in the village by the ocean, 30km from here due north-west-north.
When do we get the prize?
The drawing is in a month.
The winner will be notified through the actual mailing of the prize.
She got away.
Give back the kibi-dango!
What are you eating?
Meanwhile, Yukimura Jii-san and Sakura Baa-san were... - Next Door Neighbor
Shizuko Baa-san.
Have a peach.
Prez.
Are you sleepy?
Get some rest then.
I'll stay up for you.
You know?
Don't touch me.
I'm traveling with you guys from a turn of events, but I don't trust you guys.
Especially, you, Usui! You're too suspicious!
Inner side, the looks, and everything else are!
Then do as you please.
Hey!
Isn't that Pheasant?
He's back!
Help me! Help me!
I see something like a rope coming out of Pheasant.
Help me!
Help me! They're going to kill us!
You know? I bet he picked up a stranded ship.
How considerate of him.
Huh? So your friends are the
ones I see on that cheap boat?
What a letdown.
I don't think I can get much out of them,
so I hope you'll let me have some fun at least.
To start things out, beg for your life.
You stupid Pheasant!
Don't get captured by a pirate!
You should have sacrificed yourself!
You heartless bunch!
Could it be...?!
Is it the turtle from before?
Then, it came to say thank you?
Would you promise not to look inside?
Sure! Sure!
Mustn't peek! She must have
brought an amazing weapon!
Isn't this about to turn into another story again?
I think it'll be fine.
What is she doing?
A mysterious guy is sleeping there!
Who is he?!
Get lost!
What kind of a stupid skit was that?
That's enough!
Oh, so you were enjoying the peaches.
Meanwhile, Yukimura Jii-san and Sakura Baa-san were...
We still have plenty.
Eat all the peaches you want.
Granny...
I can't play along with this.
Oh? So you sliced the bullet with your sword?
Interesting. You come here.
Come up.
Oh fine.
No, that's impossible!
I suggest you plug your ears.
This ship is really flammable!
I think you should get away.
Yeah.
What an interesting bunch.
T-Thank you.
My pleasure.
On another note, it's morning already.
I'm tired.
Hey, look.
So it finally appears.
Oni Island!
Hey, can we really beat them?
We don't even have a weapon.
I know! At a time like this,
we'll use that little trick.
What little trick?
Tada!
Straw
A straw?
We're going to trade this
with one thing after another.
It's just a straw now, but eventually, it'll turn into an amazing weapon!
Seriously?!
You got anything to trade this with to start it out?
Tada!
Pocket Tissue
Okay, next!
Sure.
Tada!
Broken Dog Whistle
Okay, next!
Sure.
Tada!
These are all the weapons we need!
We'll go straight in!
Hey, Prez, check this out.
Oni Island Uniform - Wear this if you want to join us - Available in 3 different sizes
I see.
So, we sneak in pretending
we want to become a part of them.
What fancy looking bags
The girls may not have to face danger this way, compared to busting in.
This could be a trap in itself,
but let's try getting changed.
In that case...
We'll go scout things in a realistic version.
We'll pretend to be wild animals.
If it doesn't look like we've got
any chance, let's get out of here.
What does it look like?
T-This is...
It's a paradise!
It's a maid harem!
Don't forget our mission, Moron Trio!
We need to quickly evacuate
the girls to a safe place!
What is this about?
Is it a new girl?
Prez!
Moe~
You were a girl?!
Let's forget about these guys.
Where did Usui go to?
Right here.
Welcome home, Master.
Usui... You're....
You were fooling me?!
Did I not say that I'm an Oni?
See?
But I am the Ring Master
of the Moron Trio Circus.
Shut up! I've heard that already!
So it was you who kidnapped all these girls, too!
Prepare yourself, you pervert Oni!
Hey. What kind of wrong idea are you getting?
We live here out of our own choice.
Huh?
I was getting fed up with the lifestyle there.
The guys were dirty and selfish.
A good-looking guy showed up, so we followed him.
Then we found this island pretty cozy.
It's comfortable living and
our eyes are constantly pleased.
We're so happy right now.
So they took over my house.
How pitiful I am.
So-
Come with me, Prez.
Let's leave this island and
find some interesting place.
What are you saying!?
Why should I go with you?
Flowers of moe!
Why?
Because it turns me on to be with you.
Thus, the two started dating.
Huh?! Hold on! I haven't yet-
Wait, "yet" what?
You know, Prez, you
look so seductive in that.
Anyway, I have no intention
to be with a perv like you!
Look at that bare leg.
No! I ripped the bottom because I thought I was going to fight!
The two set off on a new trip together, but that's a whole different story.
PLACEHOLDER
Let go!
All is well that ends well.
No. Stop it, you perv!
Usui-san, what are you making Prez listen to?
She looks like she's having a nightmare.
My special folk tale.
Busy President Napping
By the way, the Moron Trio
ends up as the two's dinner,
but that's a whole different story as well.
We were food until the end...
Why?
It's horrible.
Okay. Then the Trio lived safe and sound.
Dog was named Pochi and
became Sakura Jii-san's pet.
Pochi...
Pheasant arbitrarily ate Grandmother's starch...
Monkey tricked the crab
and snagged his rice ball...
Don't kill us!
All is well that ends well.
honno sukoshi demo hakidashite hoshii
Even if it's just a little, I want you to tell me your real feelings
ほんの少しでも吐き出して欲しい
kono te de uketomeru yo
I'll accept it with these hands
この手で受け止めるよ
totemo tsuyogari na kimi no koto dakara
You're always putting on a strong front
とても強がりな君のことだから
mata nanika o kakusou to shite nee
I'm sure you're trying to hide something again
また何かを隠そうとして　ねぇ
tashika na yokan
Yeah, that must be it
確かな予感
tsukanda sono te o nigirishimete
I grabbed your hand tightly
つかんだその手を握り締めて
hashiridashita yuku ate mo naku
and started running, without anywhere in mind
走り出した　行くあてもなく
tada boku no kokoro no naka ni ite
Please just stay in my heart
ただ僕の心の中にいて
itsumo soba de mimamoru kara
Because I will always be watching over you
いつも側で見守るから
donna toki mo hanare wa shinai yo
No matter what happens, I will never leave you
どんな時も離れはしないよ
tachitomarazu kowagaranaide
So don't stop, and don't be afraid
立ち止らず　怖がらないで
kimi ga moshimo furimuita toki wa
When you do turn around and look back at me
君がもしも振り向いた時は
bokura kitto waraiaou
We will surely be smiling at each other
僕らきっと笑い会おう
Next episode preview
It pisses me off that Usui
was controlling the dream.
You like adventures,
so you enjoyed it, right?
When did I say I liked adventures?
Misaki! Check this out!
What is it, Sakura?
You're happier than ever.
There's a really cool band.
You agree right, Shizuko?
No. Not interested.
Let's have a party!
I hear we'll have a tea party with the band men.
What? Band men?
Doesn't "band men" sound new now since it's so old?
Sakura's Love is for Indies